Oh, that's right. I understand you
started a family on the other side.
How do you know that?!
I've been curious ever since I heard
about your very lovely daughter.
What do you say?
Why not introduce her to my son?
I decline.
I have His Majesty's word about my reward.
Make no contact with the Vankreift family.
I shall withdraw for now.
For now? You mean from now on, Your Highness.
Come in.
Welcome home, Lord Rovel.
Lord Sauvel returned earlier,
saying today was to be celebrated...
Alberto!
Yes, my lord?
Whether you acted for the good of this family
or not, do not anger me any further.
I'm relieving you as Sauvel's bodyguard.
Consider yourself suspended.
As you wish.
KING RAVISEL
Oh, how could this...
Rovel. It really is you, isn't it?
Mother.
Oh, I'm so glad you're safe...
I'm terribly sorry to have
been away for so long.
It's you that we're talking about, after all.
We were saying perhaps
you weren't coming home
out of adamant refusal to marry that woman.
You saw right through me. My goodness.
And yet, I never imagined
she'd marry Sauvel...
But it seems you've chased her away.
Yes.
Roren, be sure to send all of that
woman's belongings to the castle tomorrow.
It would be my pleasure.
By the way, where is Alberto?
On that matter...
I relieved him of his duties
and placed him under suspension for now.
What?
It seems he has a rather loose tongue.
He's not to be trusted.
What do you mean? Please explain.
In truth, I am already married.
I have a spirit wife and a child.
What?
This is something only a select few know.
However, Prince Ravisel has asked
to introduce his son and my daughter.
And you suspect Alberto
of telling His Highness?
Indeed. The royal family bears a curse
that prevents them from contacting spirits.
And the irritating part is that
His Highness likely intends
to use my daughter to solve that problem.
Are you saying Alberto was using
Lady Ellen as a bargaining chip?
That's right.
What treachery!
Shall I finish him off?
There's no need for that.
It would fly in the face
of my father's feelings.
Alberto felt indebted to Father.
He may have been trying to seek the royal
family's intentions regarding Agiel.
Apologies, my brother.
This is all because of how pathetic I was.
That's enough.
Well, I'll need to be cautious,
but on the positive side,
I can now introduce my wife
and daughter to society.
Rovel, are you not forgetting something?
Yes?
Shouldn't you introduce
your wife and daughter to me first?
My, my.
Mother, are you not scared?
Of what?
Of Father's mother!
That makes her your mother-in-law!
Gosh, you've already learned that
word too, Ellen? Good job!
That's not what this is about!
What are you going to do if she's scary?
It'll be fine. If things gets awkward,
we'll just never see each other again.
You're taking this so lightly...
But that's just like you, Mother.
So, when will you allow me to meet them?
Er, I'm on it.
Ori, Ellen!
Darling!
Father, you did a great job!
Oh, Ellen!
My, my, my!
Mother, let me introduce you
to my wife, Ori, and my daughter, Ellen.
Could it be? Is this woman your spirit?
Indeed, she is the spirit queen.
It's been a while.
In this world, I'm known by such names as
the Primordial King or Mother of All Things.
My heavens...
Your granddaughter will be the
next queen of the spirit world.
Please regard the two of us with open arms.
Go on, Ellen.
Nice to meet you. I'm Ellen.
To think my granddaughter is going
to be the future spirit queen...
How wonderful!
Will you call me grandma?
Huh?
Is it really okay
to get all familiar like that?
Maybe "Grandmother" would feel less rude?
Gra... Gra... Gra...
Grammie!
Did you hear that?!
Hey, did you catch that?!
My goodness, how adorable!
Truly, isn't she?! Lady Ellen is
such a splendid, precious child!
Pawpaw...
Oh? Roren, you're having her call you pawpaw?
You've got good taste.
Precisely, milady!
When Lady Ellen calls me that,
I feel so young again!
Ellen's rather popular.
Here, help yourself.
Dessert! I'm so excited!
Wait... They might still be testing me.
My, you've gotten all quiet.
What's the matter?
Here, have some.
Most impressive. Is dining etiquette
the same in the spirit world?
No, seeing as we spirits rarely eat.
Did you teach her table manners, dear?
No, I didn't teach her a thing.
My, even the way she eats is so adorable!
Ellen.
Here. Say, "Ah!"
Ah!
Mother! Feeding her is all well and good,
but at this rate, you'll spoil her dinner.
Oh dear.
My, I'm sorry, Ellen.
But she looks just precious
even when she's disappointed!
Sauvel, about moving forward...
Shall I assist you on the business side?
If possible, I would like to refrain
from joining the knights.
You're truly going to assist me?
Yes. Although I won't be able to live here,
since I have Ori and Ellen.
Oh, is that so?
My powers are too great to stay here.
They would affect the human world.
My power of harvest could easily
turn this area into a forest.
My!
And what kind of spirit are you, Ellen?
A flower perhaps?
It's okay.
I can control... elements.
Elements?
Um... Elements are
the building blocks of matter.
There are countless combinations of them,
and most substances are made up
of said combinations.
HUH?
Oh, shoot! How should I explain this?
Do you see this? It's charcoal.
But if I use my powers to change
its crystal structure...
Here we are!
Oh, that's a diamond just like my ring.
That's right!
Charcoal turned into something this beautiful?
To be honest, I don't understand it myself.
It's difficult to explain spirit
powers to humans, isn't it?
Does that mean you can
freely produce minerals?
I can!
Here, some gold.
Brother, this is...
What do you think?
You can sell it if you want.
We mustn't, Ellen.
There'd be a huge uproar if we put
something so rare out into the world.
Then we should just do this.
Here you go. For you, Grammie.
My!
Goodness...
Hey, Ellen, what are you going
to do with that mountain of gold?
Oh...
You're making too much, sweetie.
I'll be careful from now on.
To make up for Agiel's squandering,
use this toward public funds
to benefit the citizens.
It's yours.
Then that's what I shall do.
Oh, but it could put the marketplace in turmoil,
so it may be better to mix
in some impurities before selling it.
Lady Ellen, are you certain
you're all right with this?
I am. Please buy me cake again!
Most certainly! I could probably
buy one the size of this mansion.
Ellen's powers are truly something.
Right? Which is why we can't let the
royal family find out about them.
Yes. No one is to breathe a word of this.
And if we are to sell the gold,
we must prepare an origin for it.
Do you own a mine somewhere?
I can make it so that it can
be excavated from there.
Huh? Did I say something I shouldn't have?
What a clever child.
Speaking of mines, I believe
we have a small one.
In that case, I'll include things mined
there to avoid suspicion.
Amazing! She's spouting ideas
that would put adults to shame.
I am an adult on the inside, after all.
If there's anything I can help with on the
business side, please do let me know.
Hold it right there, Miss Ellen...
Everyone, listen up!
Agiel has returned to the royal family.
Well done tolerating her all this time!
As you can see, not only has my older brother
come back to us, but our family has grown.
A joyous occasion indeed.
So tonight, although small,
we've decided to throw this party.
Everyone, I'm sorry it took this long.
Also, thank you for the preparations tonight.
Now, everyone, drink up
and enjoy yourselves. Cheers!
Cheers!
Lady Ellen, would you like more juice?
Pawpaw, this is delicious!
I will have to compliment the chef.
Yes, I see.
Pawpaw? What are you doing?
For the future, I'm keeping record
of all of your favorite things.
Thank you, Pawpaw!
Roren, your expressions are losing their edge.
Most certainly, Your Grace.
It is rare to find someone
so worth fawning over.
I am itching to show my skills!
My, Roren.
Ellen must truly understand
the hearts of our servants.
You're so clever.
You're going to stop reporting to me?
Yes.
Lord Rovel caught on and dismissed me
from Lord Sauvel's side.
Oh, I see. That was quick.
I'd expect no less of Rovel.
Did you speak to the daughter?
Yes.
Perfect.
Then could you do one last job for me?
Sauvel, that was a wonderful party.
I'm pleased to hear you say so, Mother.
Now then, I think it's best we start
heading back to the spirit world.
Yes.
- What?
- My word!
- Already?
- You're going already?
Are you certain you want a forest in your yard?
What about Ellen?
Yes, what about Lady Ellen?
Well, Ellen doesn't have
that sort of power, right?
That's right.
Then let's have you sleep over tonight!
A sleepover?
Yeah. It might be good to enjoy the
human world once in a while, Ellen.
It seems Father wants some alone
time with Mother, so that's what I'll do.
Oh dear.
There should be a limit to your cleverness.
I got the hint.
We'll come in the morning, okay?
Be a good girl, Ellen.
You're tired, aren't you, Ellen?
Do you want to go sleepy-bye with Grammie?
Okie.
I will have your rooms ready right away.
You go on to bed.
Grammie is going to take a bath,
so lie down and rest.
Okie.
Lady Ellen, please wake up. Lady Ellen.
Uncle Alberto?
Take this.
For me?
Oh, it's from Mr. Blackheart...
Prince Ravisel.
The royal family bears a curse
that prevents them from contacting spirits.
And the irritating part is that
His Highness likely intends
to use my daughter to solve that problem.
Do you hate my family, Uncle?
Of course I don't!
Pardon my rudeness.
My father is very angry with you.
I am aware.
I think what you did
with good intentions was
something my father and the others consider
to be unwelcome interference.
My father and I are both
half-human and half-spirit.
In the royal family's eyes,
that makes us valuable assets.
However, in our eyes, it's a big nuisance.
Why is that?
Since the royal family remains
completely unaware of their faults,
this cursed cycle will never end...
They've forgotten they
incurred the spirits' wrath,
and even the reason behind it...
That arrogance speaks for itself.
Is this invite from him personally?
Uncle, immediately cut ties with His Highness.
If Father finds out about this,
he'll surely punish you.
I'm aware of that.
It's obvious that His Highness
doesn't care for you one bit, Uncle.
That blackhearted man won't care
if my family turns you away.
If you feel indebted to this family,
reevaluate what's really important.
My apologies, Lady Ellen...
That said, I think Father has probably
already picked up on the situation
and is watching from somewhere as we speak.
I'll persuade him.
Also, please tell Mr. Blackheart that I must
decline so as not to anger my father.
Yes, milady.
Well then, good night.
Good morning.
Grammie, good morning!
My goodness! You truly are adorable!
Lady Isabella, you are
going to crush Lady Ellen.
Here you go.
Pawpaw, thank you!
So adorable!
Morning, Ellen.
Father, good morning. Did you get
to have some lovely alone time with Mother?
Of course I did...
Wait, not that!
Ellen, don't you have something else
to say to your father?
Yes.
Uncle Alberto has cut ties with His Highness,
so I ask that you lift his suspension.
Ellen!
Father, don't you have
something to say to me?
What is this about?
Father was convinced that a messenger
from the prince would come see me,
so he deliberately had me
stay here alone last night.
Explain yourself, Rovel.
He's just being overprotective.
Now that His Highness knows of my existence,
there's no way he'll leave me be.
I think you're already aware,
but I burned the prince's letter
without reading it.
What? You burned a letter
from the prince without reading it?
What is this about?
This was a way of getting back at Father.
My...
Besides that...
Please have a proper talk with Uncle Alberto.
Until then, I won't speak to you, Father!
Wh-What?! Please don't say that, Ellen!
Oh, I can't win against my daughter.
It's hard to believe that Lady Ellen
is so keen at her age.
I was deeply touched.
Roren... Whose side are you on, anyway?
Lady Ellen's, of course.
Figures.
I presume you understood
what she was trying to tell you.
Yeah. The reason Ellen burned
the letter without reading it
was to prevent leaving any evidence
of Alberto's connection to Ravisel.
Without that, there's no proof.
She saved Alberto.
Phenomenally done.
Goodness, just who does she get it from?
What are you saying?
Lady Ellen is the spitting image
of you, my lord.
That's the problem.
You say she burned my letter
without reading it?
Yes.
As I have stated, this will be our last meeting.
If you'll excuse me.
She guessed my intentions and came back
with an even more surprising response.
Reminds me of how I used
to interact with Rovel.
I want her even more now.
She's the key to solving the mystery of why the
royal family cannot form pacts with spirits.
Of that much I am sure.
TRANSLATION: YUKARI MURASE-LOUDEN
EDITING: RILEY DALTON
QUALITY CHECK: ASHLEY BARBOZA
TRANSLATION CHECK: ELIZABETH ELLIS